ERIC THORFINNSON

Web Developer / Musician

EXPERIENCE

Music Teacher | Elite Music Academy

JUN 2017 - 2019, TORONTO, ON

 Taught Guitar, Drums, Piano, Ukulele and Music Theory to hundreds of students from ages 4-65

AV Technician | Park Boulevard Productions

JAN 2013 - 2015, NYC, NY

- Mixed and helped set up sound for a wide variety of corporate events across NYC
- Worked at the New York Public Library with clients such as Mike Tyson and Neil Gaiman

Assistant Engineer | Strange Weather Recording

JAN - NOV 2013, BROOKLYN, NY

- Assisted Lead Engineer with a variety of tasks from running Pro Tools to studio upkeep
- Worked on sessions with clients such as Yeasayer and O.A.R.

Band Founder/Leader | Autocatalytica

JAN 2009-Present

- Lead Guitar/Vocals, Writer, Composer, and Engineer
- Composed, Engineered and Released 3 records

PROJECTS

Not Your Thoughts - www.notyourthoughts.com

Deployed February 2020

- Full-stack mindfulness-based gamified journalling web app
- Developed with the MERN stack

EDUCATION

BrainStation | Diploma, Web Development

SEP 2019 - DEC 2019, TORONTO, ON

Berklee College Of Music | Bachelors in Music Production & Engineering

MAY 2008 - 2012, BOSTON, MA

Dean's List 2008-2010

ethorf@gmail.com 289-838-2835 www.ethorf.com linkedin.com/ericthorfinnson github.com/ethorf

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, Javascript, Pro Tools, Sibelius

PROFILE

My goal is to empower people to create mindful and sustainable relationships through their use of technology.

INTERESTS

I am deeply fascinated by how understanding the human mind can help us actively work to better ourselves, our planet, and our relationships. I have a voracious appetite for books, art and travel, and have been a serious meditator for over a decade.